export default [
  {
    id: 1,
    question:
      "Your direct report is hopeful, but inexperienced. What leadership style should you choose?",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S2",
      },
      {
        content: "D3",
      },
      {
        content: "Micro management",
      },
      {
        content: "S1",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S1",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question:
      "You are collaborative and encouraging when your direct report asks you about a task they're working on. What leadership style best fits this behavior?",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S3",
      },
      {
        content: "Affinity Bias",
      },
      {
        content: "Delegate",
      },
      {
        content: "S1",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S3",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question:
      "You feel overwhelmed and demoralized by the project you're working on. What development level best fits how you feel?",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "D -1",
      },
      {
        content: "D10",
      },
      {
        content: "D2",
      },
      {
        content: "D1",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "D2",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "Your direct report has taken on a new critical project and you're confident in their abilities. They've shown themselves to be consistently competent and self-directed. What development level is your direct report?",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "D1",
      },
      {
        content: "D4",
      },
      {
        content: "S4",
      },
      {
        content: "Rockstar",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "D4",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "This leadership behavior is most commonly referred to as the 'Directing' style.",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S4",
      },
      {
        content: "S2",
      },
      {
        content: "S1",
      },
      {
        content: "S3",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S1",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question:
      "This leadership behavior is most commonly referred to as the 'Coaching' style.",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S4",
      },
      {
        content: "S2",
      },
      {
        content: "S1",
      },
      {
        content: "S3",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S2",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "This leadership behavior is most commonly referred to as the 'Supporting' style.",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S4",
      },
      {
        content: "S2",
      },
      {
        content: "S1",
      },
      {
        content: "S3",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S3",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question:
      "This leadership behavior is most commonly referred to as the 'Delegating' style.",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S4",
      },
      {
        content: "S2",
      },
      {
        content: "S1",
      },
      {
        content: "S3",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S4",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question:
      "What is the most appropriate leadership style for someone who is capable, but cautious? They contribute, but are also self-critical.",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S4",
      },
      {
        content: "S3",
      },
      {
        content: "S1",
      },
      {
        content: "F1",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S3",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "This leadership style involves their direct report in problem solving and decision making and also provides frequent feedback and encouragement.",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S3",
      },
      {
        content: "S2",
      },
      {
        content: "S4",
      },
      {
        content: "Go Chiefs",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S2",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    question:
      "Your direct report was enthusiastic to pivot their role and take on a new project after Housecall acquired ServiceTitan. However, a couple weeks into the project, you notice they're becoming frustrated and discouraged. What development level did they start at and what level are they at now? ",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "S3 > S1",
      },
      {
        content: "S2 > S1",
      },
      {
        content: "S1 > S2",
      },
      {
        content: "S1 > S3",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "S1 > S2",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question:
      "If your manager asks you to teach or mentor others on your team, that means they likely think you're at which development level?",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "Enlightenment",
      },
      {
        content: "D4",
      },
      {
        content: "D1",
      },
      {
        content: "D3",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "D4",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      'If you say "Try this a few times before we meet next week", your direct report is likely at this development level.',
    answers: [
      {
        content: "D4",
      },
      {
        content: "D1",
      },
      {
        content: "D2",
      },
      {
        content: "D3",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "D1",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question:
      "Which of the following is something a leader using the S3 leadership style would say to their direct report.",
    answers: [
      {
        content: "What's getting in your way? How can I help?",
      },
      {
        content:
          "You've exceeded my expectations by completing this project with so much attention to detail.",
      },
      {
        content: "First you need to do this, then you should do that.",
      },
      {
        content:
          "Since you're still learning, would it be helpful if I provided some direction?",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "What's getting in your way? How can I help?",
  },
];
